<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on fillis lee</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on fillis lee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:15:59 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day 4</title>
      <link>/posts/day4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:15:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/day4/</guid>
      <description>Today was my last day at superluminar. I learned how to use aws and kind off played a little bit with it. On monday i will be at carpetlight.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Today was my last day at &lt;a href=&#34;https://superluminar.io/&#34;&gt;superluminar&lt;/a&gt;. I learned how to use aws and kind off
played a little bit with it. On monday i will be at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.carpetlight.com/&#34;&gt;carpetlight&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3</title>
      <link>/posts/day3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 11:15:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/day3/</guid>
      <description>On the third day I learned what an API is, with a API tutorial. I also took a quiz about graphQL.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;On the third day I learned what an API is, with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://zapier.com/learn/apis/&#34;&gt;API tutorial&lt;/a&gt;.
I also took a quiz about &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.howtographql.com/react-apollo/0-introduction/&#34;&gt;graphQL&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>/posts/day2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 15:15:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/day2/</guid>
      <description>On day two i learned a bit about JavaScript, did a tutorial quiz aubout it. And then in the end made a tictactoe game to apply, what i have just learned.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;On day two i learned a bit about JavaScript, did a tutorial quiz aubout it.
And then in the end made a tictactoe game to apply, what i have just learned.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>/posts/day1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 15:15:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/day1/</guid>
      <description>This is my first day at superluminar, today i learned how to use github and create this website. I will be giving an update everyday.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;This is my first day at superluminar, today i learned how to use github and
create this website. I will be giving an update everyday.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
