<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on fillis lee</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on fillis lee</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:15:59 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Day 7</title><link>/posts/day7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:15:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/day7/</guid><description>Today i first had to collect a few photographs visitcards, to advertise the lights to. After that i build a atom in the E Werkstatt and started building a roobot, that i will later even have to code.</description><content>&lt;p>Today i first had to collect a few photographs visitcards, to advertise the lights to. After that i build a atom in the E Werkstatt and started
building a roobot, that i will later even have to code.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Day 6</title><link>/posts/day6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 11:15:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/day6/</guid><description>Today i first had some sewing lessons and then made a little bag, to store a tiny light. I acidently did not cut the fabric right at the start, so it was a little long and thin.</description><content>&lt;p>Today i first had some sewing lessons and then made a little bag, to store a tiny light.
I acidently did not cut the fabric right at the start, so it was a little long and thin.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Day 5</title><link>/posts/day5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 11:15:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/day5/</guid><description>Today was my first day at carpetlight, first i was given an introduction, after that i had a conversation about how the marketing works. Then i had lunch break and about 14:00 i was in the Textil-werkstatt, where i will be sewing a bag tomorrow</description><content>&lt;p>Today was my first day at carpetlight, first i was given an introduction, after that i had a conversation about how the marketing works.
Then i had lunch break and about 14:00 i was in the Textil-werkstatt, where i will be sewing a bag tomorrow&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Day 4</title><link>/posts/day4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:15:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/day4/</guid><description>Today was my last day at superluminar. I learned how to use aws, which is a cloud system from amazon and kind off played a little bit with it. On monday i will be at carpetlight.</description><content>&lt;p>Today was my last day at &lt;a href="https://superluminar.io/">superluminar&lt;/a>. I learned how to use aws, which is a cloud system from amazon and kind off
played a little bit with it. On monday i will be at &lt;a href="https://www.carpetlight.com/">carpetlight&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Day 3</title><link>/posts/day3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 11:15:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/day3/</guid><description>On the third day I learned what an API is, with an API tutorial. I also took a quiz about graphQL.</description><content>&lt;p>On the third day I learned what an API is, with an &lt;a href="https://zapier.com/learn/apis/">API tutorial&lt;/a>.
I also took a quiz about &lt;a href="https://www.howtographql.com/react-apollo/0-introduction/">graphQL&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Day 2</title><link>/posts/day2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 15:15:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/day2/</guid><description>On day two i learned a bit about JavaScript, did a tutorial quiz aubout it. And then in the end made a tictactoe game to apply, what i have just learned.</description><content>&lt;p>On day two i learned a bit about JavaScript, did a tutorial quiz aubout it.
And then in the end made a tictactoe game to apply, what i have just learned.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Day 1</title><link>/posts/day1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 15:15:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/day1/</guid><description>This is my first day at superluminar, today i learned how to use github and create this website. I will be giving an update everyday.</description><content>&lt;p>This is my first day at superluminar, today i learned how to use github and
create this website. I will be giving an update everyday.&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>